A Guide to the Social Movements Collection, ca. 1959-1989, 2000, and n.d.
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series I: Topical Files
  - Helms for Senate n.d. (Box-folder 6:31)
  - High Frontier 1983, n.d. (Box-folder 6:32)
  - High Times n.d. (Box-folder 6:33)
  - Highlander Center 1983 (Box-folder 6:34)
  - Hodges for Congress Rainbow Campaign 1986 (Box-folder 6:35)
  - Hopkins House Nursing and Rehabilitation Center 1988 (Box-folder 6:36)
  - Houston 12 Defense Committee n.d. (Box-folder 6:37)
  - Hovey Street Press n.d. (Box-folder 6:38)
  - Human Service Employees Registration and Voter Education Campaign, Human Serve Fund 1983-1987, n.d. (Box-folder 6:39)
  - Hunger Strike Fighting Fund n.d. (Box-folder 6:40)
  - In the Public Interest 1977-1984, n.d. (Box-folder 6:41)
  - In These Times n.d. (Box-folder 6:42)
  - Independent Action 1984, n.d. (Box-folder 6:43)
  - The Independent American 1978-1979 (Box-folder 6:44)
  - Indochina Mobile Education Project n.d. (Box-folder 6:45)
  - Indochina Peace Campaign n.d. (Box-folder 6:46)
  - Indochina Resource Center 1972-1976, n.d. (Box-folder 6:47)
  - Indochina Solidarity Committee 1975, n.d. (Box-folder 6:48)
  - Industrial Workers of the World n.d. (Box-folder 6:49)
  - INFACT: Infant Formula Action Coalition 1983-1984, n.d. (Box-folder 6:50)
  - Inside Track from In These Times 1985 (Box-folder 6:51)
  - The Institute for Economic Research 1988 (Box-folder 6:52)
  - Institute for Independent Social Journalism, Inc. 1981 (Box-folder 6:53)
  - Institute for Policy Studies 1986-1988 (Box-folder 6:54)
  - Interfaith Center on Corporate Responsibility n.d. (Box-folder 6:55)
  - Interfaith Peace Coalition: Charlottesville, Virginia 1983 (Box-folder 6:56)
  - Internal Revenue Service (IRS) n.d. (Box-folder 6:57)
  - International Chemical Workers n.d. (Box-folder 6:58)
  - International Coalition Against Violent Entertainment n.d. (Box-folder 6:59)
  - International Committee 1973-1976 (Box-folder 6:60)
  - International Committee for United Front International Labor Defense 1980 (Box-folder 6:61)
  - International Marxist Group 1971 (Box-folder 6:62)
  - International Moneyline n.d. (Box-folder 6:63)
  - The Interreligious Foundation for Community Organization n.d. (Box-folder 7:1)
  - Inter-University Committee for Debate on Foreign Policy 1967 (Box-folder 7:2)
  - Inter-University Committee to Stop Funding War and Militarism n.d. (Box-folder 7:3)
  - Iranian Students Association in the United States (ISAUS) 1977 (Box-folder 7:4)
  - Irish Northern Aid (Box-folder 7:5)
  - Iskra: The College of William and Mary 1967 (Box-folder 7:6)
  - Israel Bonds n.d. (Box-folder 7:7)
  - Israeli Socialist Organization (MATZPEN) 1967-1969, n.d. (Box-folder 7:8)
  - Jane Wells Schooley 1984 (Box-folder 7:9)
  - Jerry Falwell 1983-1984, n.d. (Box-folder 7:10)
  - Jesse Jackson 1984-1988 (Box-folder 7:11)
  - Jewish Identity Center n.d. (Box-folder 7:12)
  - Jim Morris: Environmental T-Shirts 1988 (Box-folder 7:13)
  - Jobs With Peace Campaign 1986-1987, n.d. (Box-folder 7:14)
  - John V. Briggs Assemblyman 1976 (Box-folder 7:15)
  - John Brown Anti-Klan Committee 1980-1981 (Box-folder 7:16)
  - John Brown Education Project 1974 (Box-folder 7:17)
  - John Buenfil: Correspondence 1966-1968, n.d. (Box-folder 7:18)
  - John Buenfil: Papers 1963-1966, n.d. (Box-folder 7:19)
  - Joseph Dilys, Liberty Bell Publications 1967 (Box-folder 7:20)
  - June 12 Rally Committee 1982 (Box-folder 7:21)
  - June 14 Civil Disobedience Campaign 1982 (Box-folder 7:22)
  - Justice for All 1970 (Box-folder 7:23)
  - Justice for Huey P. Newton and the Black Panther Party 1976 (Box-folder 7:24)
  - Justice for Ireland Committee 1983, n.d. (Box-folder 7:25)
  - Kampuchea Support Committee n.d. (Box-folder 7:26)
  - The Kansas Free Press n.d. (Box-folder 7:27)
  - Karen Silkwood Fund 1983 (Box-folder 7:28)
  - The Karl Armstrong Defense Committee n.d. (Box-folder 7:29)
  - Kent Conrad for United States Senate 1986 (Box-folder 7:30)
  - Kent State University n.d. (Box-folder 7:31)
  - Kol Koreh School for Civil Liberties and Democratic Leadership n.d. (Box-folder 7:32)
  - Kristina Berster Defense Committee 1979 (Box-folder 7:33)
  - The LaRouche Cult 1982 (Box-folder 7:34)
  - The Latin American Support Committee n.d. (Box-folder 7:35)
  - Lavender Left Network n.d. (Box-folder 7:36)
  - League of Conservation Voters 1984, n.d. (Box-folder 7:37)
  - League of Women Voters Education Fund 1985, n.d. (Box-folder 7:38)
  - Lew Costello for Congress 1984 (Box-folder 7:39)
  - Lexington Grand Jury Defense Fund 1976 (Box-folder 7:40)
  - Liberal Action Committee n.d. (Box-folder 7:41)
  - Liberation Support Movement n.d. (Box-folder 7:42)
  - Live Without Trident: King's Bay n.d. (Box-folder 7:43)
  - Lloyd Doggett n.d. (Box-folder 7:44)
  - Los Angeles Draft Resistance Support Committee 1983 (Box-folder 7:45)
  - Love Revolution 1983 (Box-folder 7:46)
  - Lubavitch Youth Organization 1985 (Box-folder 7:47)
  - Maine Nuclear Referendum Committee 1981-1982, n.d. (Box-folder 7:48)
  - March Against the Draft n.d. (Box 7:49)
  - March on Washington: 20th Anniversary 1983 (Box-folder 7:50)
  - Margaret Randall Legal Defense Committee: Center for Constitutional Rights n.d. (Box-folder 7:51)
  - Marian Davis Scholarship Fund 1983-1987, n.d. (Box-folder 7:52)
  - Martin Sostre Defense Committee n.d. (Box-folder 7:53)
  - Mary Washington College: Hanover Symposium 1966 (Box-folder 7:54)
  - Maryknoll Sisters Office of Social Concerns n.d. (Box-folder 7:55)
  - Maryland Center for United Labor Action n.d. (Box-folder 7:56)
  - Mass Open Resistance 1982-1984 (Box-folder 7:57)
  - May Day 1971 Protest: Clippings 1971, n.d. (Box-folder 8:1)
  - May Day 1971 Protest: Letters and Paraphernalia 1971-1981, n.d. (Box-folder 8:2)
  - McReynolds/Drufenbrock Campaign Committee: Socialist Party USA 1980 (Box-folder 8:3)
  - Media Network: The Alternative Media Information Center 1982-1985, n.d. (Box-folder 8:4)
  - Medical Aid for El Salvador 1985-1987, n.d. (Box-folder 8:5)
  - Medical Aid for Indochina 1971-1973, n.d. (Box-folder 8:6)
  - Medical Aid for Indochina: Medicine and War Slides n.d. (Box-folder 8:7)
  - Meharry Medical College n.d. (Box-folder 8:8)
  - Meiklejohn Civil Liberties Institute 1981-1987 (Box-folder 8:9)
  - Mel Morgan for Senate 1986 (Box-folder 8:10)
  - Melanie International Fan Club: Charlottesville-Albemarle Chapter [1971] (Box-folder 8:11)
  - Mennonite Central Committee 1982-1987, n.d. (Box-folder 8:12)
  - Metro DC Anti-Weber Coalition n.d. (Box-folder 8:13)
  - Middle East Peace Project 1982 (Box-folder 8:14)
  - Middle East Research and Information Project n.d. (Box-folder 8:15)
  - Middle East Resource Center 1977-1980, n.d. (Box-folder 8:16)
  - Midwest Committee for Military Counseling 1980, n.d. (Box-folder 8:17)
  - Mike Espy 1987, n.d. (Box-folder 8:18)
  - Militarism Resource Project 1984, n.d. (Box-folder 8:19)
  - The Milwaukee 14 Defense Committee n.d. (Box-folder 8:20)
  - Minnesota Draft Help n.d. (Box-folder 8:21)
  - Minnesota Public Interest Research Group 1983 (Box-folder 8:22)
  - The Minories English Pub Protests: Charlottesville, Virginia 1975 (Box-folder 8:23)
  - Miss Manners - Judith Martin 1983, n.d. (Box-folder 8:24)
  - Mobilization Against the Draft (MAD) 1980, n.d. (Box-folder 8:25)
  - Mobilization for Survival 1979-1982, n.d. (Box-folder 8:26)
  - Mobilization to Save the Heartland 1982 (Box-folder 8:27)
  - Mondale/Ferraro Campaign n.d. (Box-folder 8:28)
  - Monthly Review 1985, n.d. (Box-folder 8:29)
  - Moral Majority, Inc. 1983-1985, n.d. (Box-folder 8:30)
  - Moslem Iranian Students Society n.d. (Box-folder 8:31)
  - Mother Jones 1981-1984 (Box-folder 8:32)
  - "Mother of the Father": Mary Washington College n.d. (Box-folder 8:33)
  - Movement Against the Draft (MAD): Charlottesville, Virginia 1980, n.d. (Box-folder 8:34)
  - Movimiento Popular de Libertacao de Angola (MPLA) Solidarity Committee 1976 (Box-folder 8:35)
  - Nashville Conference n.d. (Box-folder 9:1)
  - National Abortion Rights Action League (NARAL) 1982, n.d. (Box-folder 9:2)
  - National Action for a Fair Budget n.d. (Box-folder 9:3)
  - National Action/Research on the Military-Industrial Complex (NARMIC) 1971-1974, n.d. (Box-folder 9:4)
  - National Action/Research on the Military-Industrial Complex (NARMIC): Automated Air War Slideshow Accompanying Materials 1971-1972, n.d. (Box-folder 9:5)
  - National Anti-Klan Network n.d. (Box-folder 9:6)
  - National Anti-Draft Network n.d. (Box-folder 9:7)
  - National Association for Irish Freedom 1974-1981, n.d. (Box-folder 9:8)
  - National Campaign for No-First-Use of Nuclear Weapons n.d. (Box-folder 9:9)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) Special Contribution Fund 1984 (Box-folder 9:10)
  - National Association of Arab Americans (NAAA) 1982-1988, n.d. (Box-folder 9:11)
  - National Association of Railroad Passengers 1983-1988, n.d. (Box-folder 9:12)
  - National Campaign to Free Mayor Eddie Carthan and the Tchula 7 and to Preserve Black Political Rights 1983, n.d. (Box-folder 9:13)
  - National Campaign to Restore Abortion Funding 1984 (Box-folder 9:14)
  - National Center for Public Policy Research n.d. (Box-folder 9:15)
  - National Coalition for the Homeless 1987, n.d. (Box-folder 9:16)
  - National Coalition on Television Violence n.d. (Box-folder 9:17)
  - National Committee Against Repressive Legislation (NCARL DC) 1983-1987, n.d. (Box-folder 9:18)
  - National Committee Against U.S. Recognition of Communist Vietnam n.d. (Box-folder 9:19)
  - National Committee for an Effective Congress (NCEC) 1986-1988, n.d. (Box-folder 9:20)
  - National Committee for the Defense on Joanne Chesimard and Clark Squire 1974 (Box-folder 9:21)
  - National Committee of Taxpayers Against the Big Bank Bailout 1983 (Box-folder 9:22)
  - National Committee to Abolish HUAC/HISC (House Committee on Internal Security) n.d. (Box-folder 9:23)
  - National Committee to Free Bobby Williams n.d. (Box-folder 9:24)
  - National Committee to Support the Marion Brothers 1980-1982, n.d. (Box-folder 9:25)
  - National Conference on Soviet Jewry 1986, n.d. (Box-folder 9:26)
  - National Council for a World Peace Tax Fund n.d. (Box-folder 9:27)
  - National Council for Universal, Unconditional Amnesty (NCUUA) 1977 (Box-folder 9:28)
  - National Council on the Aging, Inc. 1983-1986 (Box-folder 9:29)
  - National Emergency Civil Liberties Committee 1983-1987 (Box-folder 9:30)
  - National Federation for Decency n.d. (Box-folder 9:31)
  - National Interreligious Service Board for Conscientious Objectors (NISBCO) 1980-1987, n.d. (Box-folder 9:32)
  - National Knights of the Ku Klux Klan n.d. (Box-folder 9:33)
  - National Lawyers Guild Foundation 1979-1988, n.d. (Box-folder 9:34)
  - National League of POW-MIA Families n.d. (Box-folder 9:35)
  - National Network in Solidarity with the Nicaraguan People n.d. (Box-folder 9:36)
  - National Network in Solidarity with the People of Guatemala 1982-1983, n.d. (Box-folder 9:37)
  - National Office of the Committee to Free the Mao Tsetung Defendants 1979-1982, n.d. (Box-folder 9:38)
  - The National Organization for the Reform of Marijuana Laws (NORML) n.d. (Box-folder 9:39)
  - National Organization of Women (NOW) 1988, n.d. (Box-folder 9:40)
  - National Organization of Women (NOW): Charlottesville, Virginia Chapter 1985-1987, n.d. (Box-folder 9:41)
  - National Organization of Women (NOW): Virginia NOW 1985-1986, n.d. (Box-folder 9:42)
  - The National PAC n.d. (Box-folder 9:43)
  - National Peace Action Coalition n.d. (Box-folder 9:44)
  - National Petition for a New U.S.-Korea Policy n.d. (Box-folder 9:45)
  - National Resistance Committee 1982-1987, n.d. (Box-folder 10:1)
  - National Resistance Conference 1981 (Box-folder 10:2)
  - National Right to Life Committee, Inc. 1982-1984, n.d. (Box-folder 10:3)
  - National Sanctuary Defense Fund n.d. (Box-folder 10:4)
  - National Sign the Treaty Now Coalition n.d. (Box-folder 10:5)
  - National Socialist Party of America n.d. (Box-folder 10:6)
  - Neighbor to Neighbor 1987 (Box-folder 10:7)
  - Nest Foundation n.d. (Box-folder 10:8)
  - Network in Solidarity with the People of Guatemala (NISGUA) 1985-1986, n.d. (Box-folder 10:9)
  - New England Committee for Nonviolent Action 1970 (Box-folder 10:10)
  - New England Free Press n.d. (Box-folder 10:11)
  - New Mexico Conference of Churches 1984 (Box-folder 10:12)
  - New Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam 1969, n.d. (Box-folder 10:13)
  - New Outlook: Middle East Monthly n.d. (Box-folder 10:14)
  - New University Conference 1969, n.d. (Box-folder 10:15)
  - New York City Unemployment and Welfare Council 1977 (Box-folder 10:16)
  - New York H-Block/Armagh Committee 1981-1986 (Box-folder 10:17)
  - News and Letters Committees 1982 (Box-folder 10:18)
  - Nicaragua Medical Aid 1986-1988, n.d. (Box-folder 10:19)
  - Nicaragua Network 1986 (Box-folder 10:20)
  - Nicaragua Support Project n.d. (Box-folder 10:21)
  - Nicaragua Information Center and Action 1979, n.d. (Box-folder 10:22)
  - Nine to Five: National Association of Working Women 1983-1988, n.d. (Box-folder 10:23)
  - No Business As Usual Action Network (NBAU) n.d. (Box-folder 10:24)
  - No More Censorship Defense Fund 1987, n.d. (Box-folder 10:25)
  - Non-collaboration n.d. (Box-folder 10:26)
  - North American Congress on Latin America n.d. (Box-folder 10:27)
  - North American Regional Organization 1984 (Box-folder 10:28)
  - Northern Virginia Coalition to End the War n.d. (Box-folder 10:29)
  - Northern Virginians Against Involuntary Servitude (NVAIS) 1979 (Box-folder 10:30)
  - November 12 Coalition: March on Washington 1983 (Box-folder 10:31)
  - Nuclear Information and Resource Service (NIRS) 1984 (Box-folder 10:32)
  - Nuclear Weapons Freeze Campaign n.d. (Box-folder 10:33)
  - Nukewatch 1984-1987 (Box-folder 10:34)
  - October 18 Resistance Campaign 1982 (Box-folder 10:35)
  - Off Our Backs 1981 (Box-folder 10:36)
  - Operation Flame of Hope n.d. (Box-folder 10:37)
  - The Organizing Committee to Freeze Reagan/Bush in '84 [1984] (Box-folder 10:38)
  - The Other Jones: An Occasional Report for Mother Jones' Community Activists 1984 (Box-folder 10:39)
  - Oxfam America 1985, n.d. (Box-folder 10:40)
  - Pacific Alliance n.d. (Box-folder 10:41)
  - Pakistan Committee for Democracy and Justice n.d. (Box-folder 10:42)
  - The Palestine Arab Delegation n.d. (Box-folder 10:43)
  - Palestine Congress of North America n.d. (Box-folder 10:44)
  - Palestine Human Rights Campaign 1979 (Box-folder 10:45)
  - Palestine Solidarity Committee n.d. (Box-folder 10:46)
  - Palestine Week: George Washington University n.d. (Box-folder 10:47)
  - The Paper Trip: People's Press in Iowa City n.d. (Box-folder 10:48)
  - The Paris Commune 1971 (Box-folder 10:49)
  - Park Teter for Senator Committee n.d. (Box-folder 10:50)
  - Patriot Party 1969 (Box-folder 10:51)
  - Paul Simon 1988 (Box-folder 10:52)
  - Paul Stacy for Congress n.d. (Box-folder 10:53)
  - PAX: People Against Executions n.d. (Box-folder 10:54)
  - PAX Americas: For Peace in the Americas 1987 (Box-folder 10:55)
  - Pax Christi Charlottesville n.d. (Box-folder 10:56)
  - Peace and Democracy News 1986 (Box-folder 10:57)
  - PeacePAC: For the Prevention of Nuclear War 1984-1987, n.d. (Box-folder 10:58)
  - The Peacemaker n.d. (Box-folder 10:59)
  - Pentagon Papers Peace Project n.d. (Box-folder 10:60)
  - People for McCarthy n.d. (Box-folder 10:61)
  - People for the American Way 1985-1988, n.d. (Box-folder 10:62)
  - People's Alliance 1979 (Box-folder 10:63)
  - People's Anti-War Mobilization 1981, n.d. (Box-folder 11:1)
  - People's Coalition for Peace and Justice n.d. (Box-folder 11:2)
  - Peoples Counter-Inaugural Committee 1981 (Box-folder 11:3)
  - Peoples Press n.d. (Box-folder 11:4)
  - The People's Yorktown Rally 1981 (Box-folder 11:5)
  - A Periodical Retreat n.d. (Box-folder 11:6)
  - Personality Plus n.d. (Box-folder 11:7)
  - Philadelphia Resistance 1969-1970, n.d. (Box-folder 11:8)
  - Philadelphia Unemployment Project n.d. (Box-folder 11:9)
  - Philadelphia War Tax Resistance n.d. (Box-folder 11:10)
  - Physicians for Social Responsibility, Inc. 1981-1982, n.d. (Box-folder 11:11)
  - Piedmont Alliance for Safe Energy (PASE): Charlottesville, Virginia 1979-1981, n.d. (Box-folder 11:12)
  - Piedmont Rural Research Cooperative: Charlottesville, Virginia n.d. (Box-folder 11:13)
  - Plowshare Peace Center 1982-1983 (Box-folder 11:14)
  - Plowshares 8 Support Committee 1981, n.d. (Box-folder 11:15)
  - PM 1970 (Box-folder 11:16)
  - Political Rights Defense Fund 1981-1988, n.d. (Box-folder 11:17)
  - Potomac Alliance 1979, n.d. (Box-folder 11:18)
  - Prairie Fire Organizing Committee 1975 (Box-folder 11:19)
  - Prison Visitors' Service n.d. (Box-folder 11:20)
  - Program for Emergency Assistance, Cooperation and Education: PEACE for Guatemala 1984, n.d. (Box-folder 11:21)
  - The Progressive Foundation 1979-1985 (Box-folder 11:22)
  - Progressive Labor Party n.d. (Box-folder 11:23)
  - Progressive Student Conference: Kent State University n.d. (Box-folder 11:24)
  - Project Air War n.d. (Box-folder 11:25)
  - Project Vote 1984, n.d. (Box-folder 11:26)
  - Proletarian Warriors n.d. (Box-folder 11:27)
  - Prolifers for Survival n.d. (Box-folder 11:28)
  - Promoting Enduring Peace 1969-1987, n.d. (Box-folder 11:29)
  - Public Citizen n.d. (Box-folder 11:30)
  - Public Witness 1971 (Box-folder 11:31)
  - Pueblo to People 1984 (Box-folder 11:32)
  - Quest for Peace 1987-1988 (Box-folder 11:33)
  - Quixote Center 1981 (Box-folder 11:34)
  - Radical Education Project n.d. (Box-folder 11:35)
  - Radical Organizing Committee n.d. (Box-folder 11:36)
  - Randolph-Macon Woman's College: International Relations Club 1970 (Box-folder 11:37)
  - Regional Sanctuary 1984 (Box-folder 11:38)
  - Religious Coalition for Abortion Rights 1987 (Box-folder 11:39)
  - Religious Task Force for El Salvador n.d. (Box-folder 11:40)
  - Repeal the Draft 1970 (Box-folder 11:41)
  - Reproductive Rights National Network n.d. (Box-folder 11:42)
  - Research and Information Center on Eritrea 1983 (Box-folder 11:43)
  - Resist 1973-1983, n.d. (Box-folder 11:44)
  - Resistance Renewal 1988 (Box-folder 11:45)
  - Resistance Task Force 1983 (Box-folder 11:46)
  - Resources Mailing Lists 1983 (Box-folder 11:47)
  - Retail Store Employees Union 1975, n.d. (Box-folder 11:48)
  - Richmond Human Rights Coalition 1986-1988, n.d. (Box-folder 11:49)
  - Right On! Black Community News Service 1976 (Box-folder 11:50)
  - Rio Grande Defense Committee 1984-1986, n.d. (Box-folder 11:51)
  - Robert Bork 1987, n.d. (Box-folder 11:52)
  - Robert Clark for Congress n.d. (Box-folder 11:53)
  - Rock Against Reagan n.d. (Box-folder 11:54)
  - Ron Dellums n.d. (Box-folder 11:55)
  - Rosie Jimenez Fund n.d. (Box-folder 11:56)
  - Royal Jordanian Embassy 1971 (Box-folder 11:57)
  - Rural Vote '88 1988 (Box-folder 11:58)
  - Russ Ford Support Group 1983 (Box-folder 11:59)
  - Safe Energy Alliance of Alabama 1980 (Box-folder 11:60)
  - Safe Energy Communication Council 1982-1984, n.d. (Box-folder 11:61)
  - Saharawi Peoples Support Committee 1982, n.d. (Box-folder 11:62)
  - Salvadoran Medical Relief Fund, also Committee for Health Rights in El Salvador 1983-1988, n.d. (Box-folder 11:63)
  - San Diego County Draft Resisters Defense Fund 1982-1988, n.d. (Box-folder 12:1)
  - The San Francisco Mime Troupe n.d. (Box-folder 12:2)
  - San Francisco Women for Peace 1979 (Box-folder 12:3)
  - San Francisco Women's Centers 1979 (Box-folder 12:4)
  - Save Lebanon, Inc. 1985 (Box-folder 12:5)
  - Scanlan's Monthly 1970, n.d. (Box-folder 12:6)
  - School-Stoppers Textbook n.d. (Box-folder 12:7)
  - Science for the People 1979 (Box-folder 12:8)
  - Seacoast Clamshell 1980-1981 (Box-folder 12:9)
  - Seattle Conspiracy Defense Fund 1970 (Box-folder 12:10)
  - The Seattle Eight 1970 (Box-folder 12:11)
  - Seattle Liberation Front n.d. (Box-folder 12:12)
  - The Seattle Seven n.d. (Box-folder 12:13)
  - The Second Page 1973 (Box-folder 12:14)
  - SeniorPAC n.d. (Box-folder 12:15)
  - Shell Strike Support Committee 1973, n.d. (Box-folder 12:16)
  - Shelter for Help in Emergency (SHE) 1981, n.d. (Box-folder 12:17)
  - Shoshana (Pat Swinton) Defense Committee n.d. (Box-folder 12:18)
  - Shut Down Selective Service: October 18 Resistance Campaign 1982 (Box-folder 12:19)
  - Social Action Coalition: Charlottesville, Virginia n.d. (Box-folder 12:20)
  - Socialist Party 1980, n.d. (Box-folder 12:21)
  - Socialist Scholars Conference 1987 (Box-folder 12:22)
  - Socialist Workers Campaign 1982 (Box-folder 12:23)
  - Sojourner Truth Organization n.d. (Box-folder 12:24)
  - Solar Lobby n.d. (Box-folder 12:25)
  - Soledad Brothers Legal Committee n.d. (Box-folder 12:26)
  - Solidarity Committee 1982, n.d. (Box-folder 12:27)
  - Solidarity Publications 1986, n.d. (Box-folder 12:28)
  - Sonia Johnson for President: Citizens Party n.d. (Box-folder 12:29)
  - SOS National GI Assistance Project 1984 (Box-folder 12:30)
  - South End Press 1987 (Box-folder 12:31)
  - Southeast Asia Resource Center 1979-1984 (Box-folder 12:32)
  - Southern Africa Solidarity Project n.d. (Box-folder 12:33)
  - Southern Conference Education Fund (SCEF) 1974, n.d. (Box-folder 12:34)
  - Southern Feminist n.d. (Box-folder 12:35)
  - Southern Organizing Committee for Economic and Social Justice (SOC) 1980 (Box-folder 12:36)
  - Southern Poverty Law Center 1987-1988 (Box-folder 12:37)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee: Activities-miscellaneous 1965-1969, n.d. (Box-folder 12:38)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee: Appalachia Region 1968-1970, n.d. (Box-folder 12:39)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee: Clippings 1969 (Box-folder 12:40)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee: Correspondence 1968-1969, n.d. (Box-folder 12:41)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee: Handbooks and Prospectuses 1967-1969 (Box-folder 12:42)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee: Internal Affairs 1966-1969, n.d. (Box-folder 12:43)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee: Literature and Speakers Lists 1968, n.d. (Box-folder 12:44)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee: Mailing Lists n.d. (Box-folder 12:45)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee: Miscellaneous Chapters 1968-1969, n.d. (Box-folder 13:1)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee: Newsletters: miscellaneous 1969-1969, n.d. (Box-folder 13:2)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee: Notes n.d. (Box-folder 13:3)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee: Press Releases 1967, n.d. (Box-folder 13:4)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee: Publications: Civil Rights and Community Organizing 1966-1967, n.d. (Box-folder 13:5)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee: Publications: The Draft n.d. (Box-folder 13:6)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee: Publications: Economics, Politics n.d. (Box-folder 13:7)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee: Publications: Labor n.d. (Box-folder 13:8)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee: Publications: Power Structure 1964-1968, n.d. (Box-folder 13:9)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee: Publications: The South n.d. (Box-folder 13:10)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee: Publications: University Reform 1964-1966, n.d. (Box-folder 13:11)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee: Publications: Vietnam and Foreign Affairs 1965-1967, n.d. (Box-folder 13:12)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee: Publications: Women's Liberation n.d. (Box-folder 13:13)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee: Richmond, Virginia Chapter - Mailings and Information 1968, n.d. (Box-folder 13:14)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee: Richmond, Virginia Chapter - Newsletters 1968-1969 (Box-folder 13:15)